IMPORTING AN ECLIPSE PROJECT
导入日食项目
Welcome to IntelliJ IDEA basics.
欢迎使用IntelliJ IDEA基础知识。
We're going to import a new Eclipse project into IntelliJ IDEA.
我们将一个新的Eclipse项目导入IntelliJ IDEA。
I've already created the project, so I'll select 'Import Project'
我已经创建了项目，因此我将选择“导入项目”
and I'll select my project jboss-as-kitchensink.
然后选择项目jboss-as-kitchensink。
I'll open that up
我把它打开
and the wizard will guide me through the process.
向导将指导我完成整个过程。
We support importing an Eclipse model, so we'll select that and click 'Next'.
我们支持导入Eclipse模型，因此我们将选择它并单击“ Next”。
There are a few options to choose from.
有一些选项可供选择。
You'll select your directory here, we can refine that if it's a subdirectory
您将在此处选择目录，如果它是子目录，我们可以对其进行优化
and you can add a module file near the classpath.
您可以在类路径附近添加一个模块文件。
It can be either an idea (directory based) or an ipr (file based) project format.
它可以是想法（基于目录）或ipr（基于文件）项目格式。
Finally, we can create a link between IntelliJ IDEA and Eclipse
最后，我们可以在IntelliJ IDEA和Eclipse之间创建链接
so, if you have team members using Eclipse and you use IntelliJ IDEA,
因此，如果您有使用Eclipse的团队成员并且使用IntelliJ IDEA，
you can link those two together so that, whenever you add a module,
您可以将这两个链接在一起，以便在添加模块时
that'll create a new Eclipse project and viceversa.
这将创建一个新的Eclipse项目，反之亦然。
It'll keep those in synch if we add this link here.
如果我们在此处添加此链接，则将使它们保持同步。
We can add a regular expression or pattern to detect certain test sources
我们可以添加正则表达式或模式以检测某些测试源
and so it'll identify those if we have any.
因此，如果有的话，它将识别出那些。
We'll click 'Next' and select the Eclipse projects to import.
我们将单击“下一步”，然后选择要导入的Eclipse项目。
Each Eclipse project will correspond to an IntelliJ IDEA module.
每个Eclipse项目将对应一个IntelliJ IDEA模块。
To reload the project after importing it, we can select 'Open Project Structure'
要在导入后重新加载项目，我们可以选择“打开项目结构”
to configure our project structure so we'll click 'Next' and select the JDK.
配置我们的项目结构，因此我们将单击“下一步”并选择JDK。
I'll just use 1.6 here. We'll wait for it to start up
我这里只用1.6。我们将等待它启动
and we'll configure our project structure by adding sources, paths and dependencies.
我们将通过添加源，路径和依赖项来配置我们的项目结构。
Finally, we’ll click ‘Apply’ and then ‘OK’.
最后，我们将单击“应用”，然后单击“确定”。
Our Eclipse project is now imported into IntelliJ IDEA
我们的Eclipse项目现已导入IntelliJ IDEA
with one additional IDEA module file next to the corresponding project file.
在相应的项目文件旁边带有一个附加的IDEA模块文件。
That's it. Thanks for watching and develop with pleasure!
而已。感谢您的观看和愉快的发展！
THANKS FOR WATCHING!
感谢收看！